sixwise.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy Summary**

Our goal is to provide you with the best experience possible. Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Statement describes our policy in detail, including all the security efforts we take to safeguard your information..

InnerMark, Inc. an Illinois Corporation which owns and operates the www.sixwise.com web site, cares about the privacy of each user of our web site. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.sixwise.com web site. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [webmaster@sixwise.com](mailto:webmaster@sixwise.com).

If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact with a copy / attachment of prior email communications to: [jdearlove@innermark.net](mailto:jdearlove@innermark.net)

**What Personal Information About Customers Does SixWise.com Gather?**  
Here are the types of information we gather:

**Information You Give Us**

We receive and store any information you enter on SixWise.com **** or give us in any other way. You provide information to SixWise.com **** when you register, sign-in, search, purchase products, apply for credit, participate in a contest or questionnaire, sign up for our e-mail newsletters, or communicate with customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; gender; credit card information; e-mail address; or people to whom purchases have been shipped (for example, a gift recipient), including address and phone number.

**Information Automatically Collected**  
We automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit SixWise.com. For example, like most Web sites, we use "cookies." Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click to, through, and from SixWise.com, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and phone number used to call our 888 number.

**More About Cookies**.  
We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of SixWise.com. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on SixWise.com **** and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently.

**Information from Other Sources**  
For certain reasons, such as providing you special offers that we think will be of interest, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

**_Commitment for Notification to Our Web Site_**

The SixWise.com web site agrees upon request to notify each user of the following: 

1\. What personal information of yours or a third party is collected from you if any by the SixWise.com web site. 

2\. The name of any organization having collected such information. 

3\. How the information is or may be planned to be used. 

4\. With whom the information may be shared. 

5\. What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use and distribution of such information. 

6\. The security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information which is under the control of SixWise.com. 

7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**_Information Collection and Use_**

The SixWise.com web site collects information from our users at several different points on our web site. When you use the web site, some basic, general information is collected. This general information is used internally in connection with our business to improve the web site, including our marketing and advertising efforts, and to make your use of the web site as enjoyable and efficient as possible. 

When you set up an account on our web site or purchase an item from our web site, we collect personal information provided by you that may include your: (i) first and last name; (ii) billing address; (iii) shipping address; (iv) other shipping addresses; (v) email address; (vi) phone number; (vii) credit card account number; (viii) items purchased from us; and (ix) browsing, buying and selling patterns. 

We use the above personal information you provide us in order to provide you with the goods and services that you purchase on our web site. We use your email address to provide you with information about your order and its status and we may occasionally send out emails, including newsletters, to people who have placed an order on-line, with information about other goods and services available on our web site. Your phone number is used by us only in the event that our customer service representatives need to contact you about an order you have placed.

InnerMark, Inc. (SixWise.com) owns and operates the SixWise.com web site and we are the sole owner of this information collected on the web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to a third party in any way other than as disclosed in this privacy policy. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities and may, in our sole discretion, disclose personal information or other information to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena, or government request. We reserve the right to release personal information or other information about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms of Service, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, if we believe, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate our web site or to protect the rights or property of SixWise.com, our affiliates or our officers, directors, employees, agents, third-party content providers, suppliers, sponsors, or licensors. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities we reasonably believe in our sole discretion to be unlawful. If we are legally compelled to disclose information about you to a third party, we will attempt to notify you by sending an email to the email address in our records unless doing so would violate the law or unless you have not provided your email address to us. 

To use some features on the SixWise.com web site, a user must first complete a registration form on the web site. During registration, a user is required to give contact information, such as name and email address. This information is used to contact users about the services on our web site for which they have indicated interest. It is optional for users to provide additional, demographic information, such as age and gender, but we encourage our users to provide such information so that we can provide a more personalized experience for our users on our web site.

We request additional personal information from our users when placing an order on our web site. In completing our order form, a user must provide contact information, such as name and shipping address, and financial information, such as credit card account number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill our customer orders. If we experience difficulties processing an order, we will contact a user through this information.

**_Security_**

SixWise.com uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers (SSL). SixWise.com treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your computer.

**_Safety of Credit Card Transactions_**

Every credit card purchase you make at SixWise.com will be safe. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent credit card charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, SixWise.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using SixWise.com. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

**_Business Partners and Selected Vendors We Do Not Control_**

We work closely with certain business partners and carefully selected vendors to provide you with access to their product information and offerings or to their online stores (for example, the Partners listed on SixWise.com products available at SixWise.com). We may provides links to their web sites where you choose to share your personal data, including personally identifiable information about you. We may share such information with shipping partners or ours who direct ship your selected merchandise from their facilities or shipping service providers including such business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you products and/or services that may be of interest to you through the mail or the internet. If you choose to access the Partners, disclose information to the Partners, place orders from the Partners, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their applicable privacy policies. To prevent our disclosure of your personally identifiable information to one of these third parties, you can choose not use their services or order their products. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services or place orders with them for their products.

**_Agents_**

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, performing credit checks and approvals, processing credit card payments, collecting on delinquent accounts and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, _but may not use it for other purposes_.

## _Cookies_

A cookie is a text file stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Web sites create cookies to record information about a user's preferences, such as the items you add to your shopping cart, and for security purposes (see _Security_ below). Cookies are also used to help us determine the various services you use and the support you may need, and to help us detect and solve any problems you may have while using our web site. In addition, the use of a cookie on our web site will enable users to log on without having to reenter their password on each visit and to fully participate in our Community discussions. Most cookies expire after a certain time period. If you wish, you may set your browser to reject all cookies and still view our web site. Because our online ordering system requires cookies, you will not be able to order online, but you can still place an order by phone, fax or mail. 

**_Log Files_**

Like most standard web sites, we use log files on our servers. These log files store information regarding IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. These log files are used to analyze trends, administer the web site, track user's movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for our use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personal information.

**_Sharing of General or Demographic Information_**

We will only share aggregated, general or demographic information we collect about our users and their use of our web site with our partners (except where noted for specific co-branded relationships below) and advertisers in a manner which does not identify any individual user. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders placed on our web site, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services purchased on our web site. These companies will not retain, share, store or use any of our user's personal information for any secondary purposes. We partner with other parties to provide specific services which are available on our web site. When a user signs up for these services, we will share the user's name or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services to the user. These parties are not allowed to use such personal information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**_Links_**

The web site contains links to other web sites. We want you to be aware that when you click on such links, including banner advertising, which take you to a third-party web site, you will be subject to such third-party's privacy policies. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites and we expressly disclaim any and all liability for the actions of third-parties, including, without limitation, actions relating to the use and/or disclosure of personal information by such third-parties. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our web site and enter a third-party web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects their personal information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by our web site.

**_Electronic Newsletters and E-Mails_**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our e-newsletter we we will ask for contact information, such as name and email address, and store this information securely. SixWise.com offers this free electronic newsletter as a service to our users. In addition, SixWise.com may periodically send you information and product promotions via e-mail. You may cancel your subscription to our electronic newsletter or end product related e-mails from SixWise.com at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every such newsletter or e-mail. You may also elect to remove your e-mail address from our newsletter and e-mail mailing lists by sending us an email.

**_Send to a Friend_**

If a user elects to use our referral service to inform a friend about a part of our web site, a form asks for the friend's name and email address. The form will automatically send the information to the friend via email. We do not store this information and the form is only used to send this one-time referral email. **_ _**

**_Public Forums: Message Boards, and Chats_**

In the future in order to post a message on our SixWise.com user information message boards or during a Chat you will be asked to sign in with your member login information. We do not use this information in any way other than to recognize you for postings nor do we disclose this information to any third parties. 

With regard to the message boards, your email address is not visible on the boards however other users are able to send you email via your nickname without your email address being displayed. When you sign in to post on the message boards a message board and chat account is created for you on message board software. SixWise.com does not collect this information and does not use it in any way other to automatically create the account nor do we at SixWise.com share this information with any third parties unless required by authorized law enforcement agencies when required.

With regard to the "Ask SixWise" feature, your name will be used if your question has been selected for use in the "Q & A" section of the website. If you do not wish your name used, our Editors can, at their discretion, omit this information from the posted Q&A if you elect to remain anonymous and so request in the body of your submitted question.

Do remember that whatever you post on the message boards, chat or to the "Ask SixWise" feature, it is considered public knowledge and you should always use caution when posting. Avoid posting your home address or phone number on a public board or chat. Although one must be a registered user to post messages the message boards are public and may be read by non-registered users.

SixWise.com reserves the right to re-publish your postings from message boards or chat rooms in any format.

**_Surveys & Contests_**

From time-to-time, our web site requests information from our users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user has a choice whether or not to provide us with such information. Information requested may include contact information, such as name and shipping address, and demographic information, such as zip code, age level. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve the use and efficiency of this web site. 

**_Security_**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about the security of our web site, you can send an email to [webmaster@SixWise.com ](mailto:webmaster@sixwise.com)

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and the e-bulletins. Each user has the option to not receive these types of communications (see _Choice/Opt-Out_ below).

Occasionally, it is necessary to send out service-related announcements. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email informing you of such service interruption. Generally, users may not opt-out of receiving these service-related communications. In addition, we communicate with our users on a regular basis to provide requested services and regarding issues relating to their account via email.

If a user's personal information changes or if a user no longer desires our service, we will enable our users to correct, update or remove from our web site the personal data they provided to us. Such changes can be made either through the member information page on our web site or by emailing our webmaster at [webmaster@SixWise.com ](mailto:webmaster@sixwise.com).

Our users are given the opportunity when registering with our web site to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the provision of goods or services through our web site. Our membership form has an opt-out mechanism so users purchasing a membership from us may elect to not have their email address added to our marketing and promotional address lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our e-bulletins or other marketing and promotional materials from us or our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to any such promotional email indicating your desire to no longer receive such emails or by emailing our webmaster at [webmaster@SixWise.com.](mailto:webmaster@SixWise.com.)

Users of our web site will be notified if, in connection with the use of a particular service on our web site, their information will be collected by any outside third-party. At such time, the user can determine whether they wish to proceed with a service that will involve an outside party having access to their information. 

The surveys, tests and quizzes SixWise.com publishes are for the sole purpose of entertainment and intellectual stimulation. These tests should not be considered scientifically accurate. None of the surveys, tests or quizzes SixWise.com publishes should be used as a medical treatment tool to diagnose health problems. SixWise Surveys develop scores compiled from the successful completion of the appropriate questionnaire, based upon weighted values in each category. SixWise makes no guarantee that tests cover all data, information, resources, etc. necessary to make a complete or accurate assessment of an individual. The information and data given on this site are not in any way designed to replace the advice of a doctor or other medical, safety, or financial professional. Sixwise Surveys are not diagnosis tools. Sixwise makes no warranty to the accuracy, completeness, usefulness, value, fairness, of the tests, nor does Sixwise guarantee against errors, failed links, omissions, or lost data on the site. Should you feel any emotional, mental, or physical problems, please contact your doctor or other medical professional immediately. T he purpose of all of the surveys, tests and quizzes on SixWise is to provide fun and useful tools to users to promote general education and understanding. For any specific questions or concerns regarding your health, consult your doctor or medical professional. If, after completing any of the tests, you have personal questions, they should be directed to your personal physician, other medical professional, or the appropriate professionals in other fields such as finances. Information on SixWise should be read with common sense and be aware that the information provided on SixWise is very general and, as such, unlikely to encapsulate your specific situation. Sixwise does not hold any responsibility or liability for any personal injury, damage or illness for your direct or indirect use of any surveys or materials on Sixwise. 

**_Business Transfers_**

As we continue to develop our business, we might buy the online and/or off-line retail operations of others. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that SixWise.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired by or transferred to another entity, customer information would likely be one of the transferred assets.

**_Government and Legal Disclosures of Your Information_**

We may disclose information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we believe necessary in connection with an investigation of illegal activity that may expose you or us to legal liability. In addition, if you have purchased products from us on extended payment terms, it may be necessary for us to file certain information about you with state or local government offices to perfect our security interest in the products so purchased, or to provide certain information about you to collection agencies in the event of non-payment or a payment dispute.

**_What Choices Do You Have?_**

You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of other SixWise.com **** features. SixWise.com **** offers the ability to correct or change the information collected through your use of SixWise.com. You can change information at any time and as often as necessary.  If you experience problems or have any questions about our services, contact us by email: [webmaster@sixwise.com](mailto:webmaster@sixwise.com). When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

To get more information about this and other highly important topics, sign up for your free subscription to our weekly SixWise.com "Be Safe, Live Long & Prosper" e-newsletter.

With every issue of the free SixWise.com newsletter, you’ll get access to the insights, products, services, and more that can truly improve your well-being, peace of mind, and therefore your life!

---|---|---|---
